TOHO CORPORATION
2,Mitsuha
Some mornings, I wake up crying
without knowing why.
3,Mitsuha
That's when everything happens
now and again.
4,Taki
Whatever that dream was I had,
I can never remember it.
5,Taki+Mitsuha
- But...
6,Mitsuha
the only thing that
does last when I wake up
7, Mitsuha
is a sense of loss,
8, Mitsuha
which lingers for a long time afterwards.
9,Taki
I'm always searching for something
10,Taki
or someone.
11,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: I've been consumed by this feeling...
12,Mitsuha
ever since that day.
13,Taki
Taki: The day... a star fell.
14,Taki
It was almost like...
15,Mitsuha
-like seeing something out of a dream.
16,Mitsuha
Nothing more or less...
17,Mitsuha+Taki
- than a breathtaking view.
18,Band
Ah, if only our voices speak at night
19,Band
could ever reach the very
edge of this world
20,Band
and of time
21,Band
instead of fading into air and dust.
22,Band
Then what will the words, could it ever be
23,Band
farthest words from "probably"?
24,Band
Let's make a promise that will never fade.
25,Band
Let's say it together on
the count of three, oh.
26,Band
Ah, I'm told that some part of
every wish will be heard,
27,Band
but lately I've lost sight of
the truth in those words.
28,Band
I can't even remember when
I gave up believing.
29,Band
What could have been the reason?
30,Band
Ah, the very moment that the rain will stop
31,Band
in the place rainbow born and dies.
32,Band
And where the end of this life lies,
33,Band
I've always been insisting there was
something that I've longing for.
34,Band
One day we'll reach to emotions
unexplored, unprecedented.
35,Band
We'll high-five love we've yet to
discover and give a kiss to time.
36,Band
The five dimensions keeps on teasing me,
37,Band
but I will keep on looking at you, dear.
38,Band
Let's make a sign for when we
say "nice to meet you" again.
39,Band
I'm on my way to you,
40,Band
chasing after your name.
41,Mitsuha
Taki...
42,Mitsuha
Taki.
43,Mitsuha
Taki!
44,Mitsuha
Don't you remember?
45,Mitsuha
My name is...
46,Mitsuha
Mitsuha!
47,Yotsuha
Sis, what are you... doing?
48,Mitsuha
Whoa, they're so realistic-feeling...
49,Yotsuha
"Sis"?
50,Mitsuha
Me?
51,Yotsuha
Are you still asleep?
52,Yotsuha
Breakfast time, hurry up!
53,Mitsuha
Huh?
54,Mitsuha
Wha-?
55,Mitsuha
WHAAAT?!
56,Yotsuha
Do you wanna have any of
last night's fish, grandma?
57,Grandma
You can eat it.
58,Mitsuha+Grandma
- Mornin'!
59,Yotsuha
Lazy butt, you're so slow!
60,Mitsuha
I'll fix breakfast tomorrow.
61,Mitsuha
Oh, that's a lot...
62,Mitsuha
-Oh, well.
63,Grandma+Mitsuha
- You're back to normal today.
- Huh?
64,Yatsuha+Mitsuha
- You were so crazy yesterday.
- What do you mean, "crazy"?
65,Radio
-Attention, citizens of Itomori.
66,Radio
Good morning!
67,Radio
This is an official announcement
from Itomori Town Hall.
68,Radio
It is in regards to the mayoral election.
69,Radio
The election will be held
on the 20th of next month.
70,Radio
The election committee would
like to remind everyone tha-
71,None
"Comet to pass by in a month:
Visible to the naked eye"
72,TV
A comet that comes only
once every 1,200 years
73,TV
will finally be headed our way in a month.
74,TV
The comet will be visible to the naked eye for
several days once it approaches the Earth...
75,Yotsuha
Just make up with him already, okay?
76,Mitsuha+TV
- That's an adult matter.
- According to JAXA's spokesperson, they're preparing for the celestial show of the millennium.
77,None
"Position of Comet Tiamat"
78,None
"Closest on October 4th"
79,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- We're leaving!
80,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: I can't wait 'til the festival!
It's gonna be so much fun!
81,Yotsuha
Study hard, sis!
82,Saya
Ah!
83,Saya
Mitsuha!
84,Mitsuha
Good mornin', Saya! Mornin', Teshi!
85,Saya+Teshi
- Mornin'!
- Come on, would you get off already?
86,Saya+Teshi
- What for, meanie?
- 'Cause you're heavy.
87,Saya+Mitsuha
- Hey, that's rude!
- Y'know, I gotta say. You two make a great couple.
88,Saya+Teshi
- No, we don't!
89,Mitsuha
Oh, I see you actually
bothered to do your hair today.
90,Mitsuha+Teshi
-Wait, what?
-Oh, yeah. What happened?
Did your grandma exorcise all your demons?
91,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Exorcise?
- Somethin' totally possessed your body!
92,Saya
Would you just give it a rest
with all this occult nonsense?
93,Saya+Mitsuha
- Mitsuha's gotta be feelin'
stressed enough as it is, right?
- What are you guys talking about?
94,Teshi
Are you feelin' okay?
95,Toshiki
And above all, restoring the town's fiscal health
so we can continue our revitalization project.
96,Toshiki
It's only when all these things are achieved
that we can create a safe and secure community.
97,Toshiki+BystanderA
- As the incumbent, my administration...
- Miyamizu's gonna get another term anyway.
98,BystanderB
I hear he's been dullin' out the pork.
Just between us.
99,StudentA+Mitsuha
- Hey, Miyamizu.
- Mornin'.
100,StudentA
Looks like the mayor and the
contractor's kid are pretty cozy, too.
101,Toshiki
-To improve the quality of
life of each and every resident.
102,Toshiki+Mitsuha
- Mitsuha!
- [Gasp]
103,Toshiki
Stand up straight when you're walking!
104,BystanderC
Oh, he's tough on his family.
105,BystanderD
Well, that's the mayor for ya.
106,StudentB+StudentC
- Awkward.
- Sucks to be her.
107,Sara
Mitsuha!
108,Mitsuha
In front of everyone.
109,None
"Who are you?"
110,Teacher
"Tasokare" [Twilight]
111,Teacher
"Two light." That's the
origin of the word twilight.
112,Teacher
I'm sure everyone here knows that word.
113,Teacher
It's dusk, a time when
it's neither day nor night.
114,Teacher
When the border between worlds blur,
115,Teacher
and one might encounter
something not human.
116,Teacher
Another older term for it is dusk light.
117,Teacher
Some people also call it "golden hour".
118,None
"Karetaso/Kawatare = Who is that?"
119,StudentD
-What about "magic hour"?
It's something my grandma says.
120,Teacher
-Well, golden hour and magic
hour are technically the same,
121,Teacher
but it's a term that
mostly photographers use.
122,None
"Who are you?"
123,StudentD+Class
- Well, she does take a lot of pictures.
- [CLASS Laughing]
124,Teacher
-Okay, next...
125,Teacher+Mitsuha
- Miyamizu!
- Uh, yes?
126,Teacher
Well, I can see that you
remember your own name today.
127,Class
[Laughing]
128,Saya+Mitsuha
Sayaka: You... don't remember?
Mitsuha: Uh-uh...
129,Sara
Well, believe it or not, you forgot where
your own desk and locker were yesterday.
130,Sara
Plus, you had the worst case of bedhead,
and you didn't have your ribbon on, either!
131,Mitsuha
What?! No way!
132,Sara
Yeah, it was like you
had amnesia or somethin'.
133,Mitsuha
Now that you mention it, I do feel like
I've been havin' weird dreams lately.
134,Mitsuha
Like a dream about someone else's life?
135,Mitsuha
It's all so fuzzy.
136,Teshi
Wait a sec, I've got it...
137,Teshi
It's memories from a previous life,
138,Teshi
or maybe your subconscious linked to the
Everett interpretation of the multiverse!
139,Sara
Keep your full mouth shut!
140,Mitsuha
Wait a minute! Teshi, don't tell me you
were the one who wrote in my noteboo... k.
141,Mitsuha
Forget it.
142,Sara
But you really were actin' just a
little funny yesterday, Mitsuha.
143,Sara
You been feelin' okay?
144,Mitsuha
That's what's weird. I feel fine.
145,Sara
Maybe it's from stress. You know, you've
got that ritual comin' up soon, don'tcha?
146,Mitsuha
Ugh, don't remind me!
147,Mitsuha
I can't stand this place anymore!
It's too small and town-ey.
148,Mitsuha
I wanna graduate already and
go to Tokyo as soon as I can!
149,Sara
-Can't say I blame you. There really
is nothin' at all in this town.
150,Sara+Mitsuha
-There's only one train that stops here every two
hours -and all the stores close at nine o' clock.
151,Sara
No bookstores, no dentists,
152,None
"Mother's" "Cat's Eye Pub"
153,Mitsuha
but two cocktail lounges
for whatever reason.
154,Sara+Mitsuha
- No jobs in town.
- No one date-able.
155,Sara
Even the days are too short.
156,Teshi
You know what?!
157,Sara+Mitsuha
- No, what?
158,Teshi
Forget that stuff.
Why don't we go to a café?
159,Sara+Mitsuha
- A café?
- Really?
160,Sara+Mitsuha
- Where?!
161,BystanderD
Hello, kids!
162,Sara+Teshi
- Hi, there!
- Evenin', ma'am!
163,Sara+Teshi
- How is this a café?
- Like this town's got a café.
164,Sara
Mitsuha just went straight home.
165,Sara+Teshi
- Things have gotta be really
rough for her right now.
- She's on center stage and all.
166,Sara
Yeah...
167,Sara+Teshi
- Hey, Teshi...
- Hm?
168,Sara
What are you gonna do after
you graduate high school?
169,Teshi
Where'd that come from?
You talkin' about the future?
170,Sara
Mh-hm.
171,Teshi
I dunno. I think I'll probably just end up
livin' in this town, y'know. Same as ever.
172,Yotsuha
I wanna do what you're doin'.
173,Grandma
It's still too soon for you to
try, Yotsuha.
174,Grandma
Listen to the thread's voice.
175,Grandma
When you twine it round and round like this, feelings
will start flowing between you and the thread.
176,Yotsuha+Mitsuha
- It's not like threads talk...
- She's telling you to focus.
177,Grandma
Etched within our braided cords is a
thousand years' worth of Itomori's history.
178,Grandma
Listen. Somethin' happened
two hundred years ago...
179,Mitsuha
Here she goes.
180,Grandma
The bathroom of sandal maker Mayugoro Yamazaki
caught on fire and this whole area burned down.
181,Grandma
The shrine and old
documents were destroyed.
182,Grandma+Mitsuha
- This is known as...
- Mayugoro's Great Fire.
183,Yotsuha
They named the fire after him?!
I feel bad for Mayugoro.
184,Grandma
The meaning behind our festivals
was lost because of that.
185,Grandma
Only the surface was left.
186,Grandma
But even if those words are
gone, those words shouldn't fade.
187,Grandma
That's the Miyamizu shrine's duty.
Our important task.
188,Grandma
Ugh...
189,Grandma
Despite all that, that son-in-law of mine!
190,Grandma
Abandoning the Shinto priesthood and leaving
this house were bad enough, but politics?!
191,Grandma
Oh, he's hopeless!
192,Toshiki
-Have another, mister foreman.
193,Toshiki+Foreman
- I'll be counting on your
help again for this election.
- Leave it to me.
194,Foreman
You'll get the votes from the
Kadoiri and Sakagami Districts, guaranteed.
195,BackCharA+BackCharB
- How's the datin' scene?
- It ain't easy, that's for sure.
196,Teshi+TeshiMom
- Smells like corruption in there.
- What are you talkin' about?
197,Foreman+TeshiMom
- We're gonna need two
or three more bottles.
- Yes, dear.
198,Foreman
Katsuhiko, you're gonna help
out at the site this weekend.
199,Foreman+Teshi
- We'll be usin' explosives,
so you better study up.
- Grngh.
200,Foreman
What was that?!
201,Teshi
Got it!
202,Teshi
Guess we both can't stand things here.
203,BystanderE
Is that Yotsuha? She's all grown up.
204,BystanderF
They're lookers, alright.
Just like their mother.
205,Teshi+Saya
- Heya!
- Hey.
206,Teshi
World's oldest kind of sake,
207,Teshi
but chewin' on rice, spittin' it out, and then
lettin' it ferment naturally, it becomes alcohol.
208,Saya
Kuchikamizake.
209,Saya
Do the gods really appreciate that.
The way it's ma-
210,Teshi
Yeah, of course they do!
211,StudentA
Hey, check it out. It's Miyamizu.
212,StudentB+StudentC
-Ugh! I'd never do that!
-And in front of everybody!
Embarrassing, right?
213,Yotsuha
You should try to cheer up, sis.
214,Yotsuha
Who cares if a few of the kids
from your school saw that?
215,Mitsuha
It must be nice for you
not being a teenager.
216,Yotsuha
Hey, I know! You should just sell
Kuchikamizake and move to Tokyo!
217,Yotsuha
I bet you could sell it with all sorts of
stuff like photos and making-of videos.
218,Yotsuha
Oh, and then you can call it "Shrine
Maiden's Sake"! You'll make buttloads!
219,None
"Shrine Maiden's Sake"
220,Mitsuha
I can't! There are liquor laws!
221,Yotsuha
That's what you have a problem with?
222,Mitsuha
I hate this town! I hate this life, too!
223,Mitsuha
Please make me a handsome
Tokyo boy in my next life!
224,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: What a jackass.
225,Taki
Ow...
226,Taki
Where...?
227,Taki
Huh?
228,Taki
Hmm?
229,Taki
Something's... there...
230,Taki
Aaaah!
231,Taki
Eh!
232,TakiDad
Taki's Father: Taki, you up?
233,TakiDad
It was your turn to cook breakfast,
wasn't it? Did you sleep in?
234,Taki
I'm sorry.
235,TakiDad
Ugh, I'm heading out.
236,TakiDad+Taki
- Finish the miso.
- Uh, okay...
237,TakiDad
Make sure you go to school,
even if you're late. Seeya.
238,Taki
H-have a nice day.
239,Taki
What a strange dream...
240,Taki
[Gasp]
241,None
"From Tsukasa: Run, you're late!"
242,Taki
Huh? It's from "Tsukasa"?
243,Taki
Who's that? Hrm.
244,Taki
Uhhh...
245,Taki
I gotta go pee.
246,Taki
Way too real...
247,None
"Shinjuku Station"
248,Taki
I'm in Tokyo!
249,None
"Jingu High School"
250,Crowd
- Where did you get this?
- Daikanyama.
251,Crowd
Guess who's opening at our next gig?
252,Crowd
- W-wait wait, we have a gig?
- Hey, let's skip club stuff
today and catch a movie.
253,Taki
Uh...
254,Tsukasa
Taaaki!
255,Tsukasa
Can't believe you got in at noon.
Come on, let's grab lunch!
256,Tsukasa
You ignored my text, too!
257,Taki+Tsukasa
- Mr. Tsukasa.
- "Mister"? You don't have to go that far.
258,Shinta+Taki
- You got lost?
- Yeah.
259,Shinta
Wait a second. How'd you wind up
getting lost on the way to school?
260,Taki
Uh...
261,Taki+Shinta
-Well, a girl-
-A girl?
262,Taki
A gal-
263,Shinta+Tsukasa
- Hm?
264,Taki
I mean...
265,Shinta+Tsukasa
- Huh?!
266,Taki
A guy...
267,Shinta+Tsukasa
- [Nod]
268,Taki
Y'know, guys just wanna have fun. Every day's a
festival when you're living in Tokyo... as a guy.
269,Shinta
Hey, you... sound funny.
270,Tsukasa
-And where's your lunch?
271,Shinta+Tsukasa
- Seriously?
- What is up with you?
272,Shinta+Tsukasa
- We could share somethin'.
- Let's make a croquette-egg sandwich.
273,Crowd
-Yes! Hahahaha!
274,Taki
Ah...
275,Taki
Thank you!
276,Shinta+Tsukasa
- Wanna hit the café later?
- Oh, that one? Sure.
277,Tsukasa
-You in, Taki?
278,Taki
-What? What?! WHAT?!
279,Taki
A café?!
280,Shinta+Tsukasa
- They've got nice timberwork in here.
- Yeah, it's pretty intricate.
281,Tsukasa
Taki, all set?
282,Taki
Uh...[Gasp]
283,Taki
I could live for a whole month
on what these pancakes cost!
284,Shinta
-Uh... maybe a decade ago.
285,Taki
-Hmmm...
286,Taki
Oh, well! It's only a dream!
287,Taki
Dreams are great!
288,Taki
Huh?
289,Taki
Wha? Oh no! I think that I'm late for work.
290,Shinta+Tsukasa
- You got a shift today?
- Guess you better get goin'.
291,Taki
Right.
292,Taki
Sorry, but uh...
293,Taki
Where exactly do I work?
294,Shinta+Tsukasa
- Wha?
295,Kitchen
- Tables six, seven, and ten are waiting!
- Table twelve! Taki!
296,Taki
Got it!
297,Taki
Here you go.
298,Taki
So, the zucchini and tomato
salad with a side of...
299,Customers+Taki
- We didn't order that!
- Wha?
300,Kitchen
- Taki! I told you that
we are out of truffles!
- Taki, you gotta talk louder!
301,Kitchen
Taki!
302,Taki
When is this nightmare gonna be over?!
303,Customers
Diner: Waiter.
304,Customers+Taki
- Hey, you.
- Uh, yes?
305,Customers
See this? Does it look right?
A toothpick's in it.
306,Customers
What would have happened if we ate it?
307,Customers
It's really lucky I noticed when I did.
308,Customers+Taki
-Do something.
-Uh... it's just that...
309,Taki
Well, I don't even think
we have toothpicks at this-
310,Customers
What?!
311,Okudera
Excuse me. Is everything alright over here?
312,Customers+Okudera
- Well, like I was trying to tell the guy...
- I'll take care of this.
313,Staff
What's wrong with you today?
314,Okudera
We truly apologize.
Your meal is on the house tonight.
315,Customers
Why, thank you.
316,Okudera
You weren't hurt, were you?
317,Taki+Staff
- Uh... Oku... dera?
- That's "Miss" to you.
318,Taki+Okudera
-Miss Okudera. About before-
-We just had some bad luck is all.
319,Taki+Okudera
-No, I- I-
-Those guys were definitely scamming us.
320,Okudera
I handled it according to the
manual, but still...
321,Staff
Uh-Ms. Okudera, your skirt!
322,Staff
- Are you alright?
- Did something happen?
323,Staff
Looks like someone cut it.
324,Okudera
That guy...
325,Staff
- Do you remember what he looked like?
- No...
326,Taki+Staff
- Come with me.
- Hey, Taki.
327,Taki
Okay, take off your skirt.
328,Okudera
What?!
329,Taki
N- wh- I'll... I'll look the other way!
330,Taki
Hold on, this won't take long.
331,Taki
All done! Ta-da!
332,Okudera
You're really good, Taki!
It's way cuter now!
333,Taki
By the way, I wanted to thank you for
all your help with that customer earlier.
334,Okudera
To be honest, well...
I was worried about you.
335,Okudera
You aren't that strong,
but you're quick to pick a fight.
336,Okudera
I like you better today.
337,Okudera
You've got a feminine side.
Who woulda guessed?
338,None
"JR Yamanote Line: 7 min."
339,Taki
I gotta say,
this dream sure does seem real.
340,Taki
Ah, looks like he keeps a journal.
341,Taki
So organized.
342,Taki
I wish I lived in Tokyo.
343,Taki
One of her.
344,Taki
Unrequited love?
345,None
"Walked to the station with Ms. Okudera
after work, thanks to my feminine powers!"
346,None
"Who are you?"
347,None
"Mitsuha"
348,Taki
What is this?
349,None
"Mitsuha"
350,Taki
Wha?!
351,Taki
What?!
352,None
"Thanks to my feminine powers!"
353,Taki
What is going on?!
354,Shinta
So, café today?
355,Taki
Thanks, but I gotta go to work.
356,Tsukasa
Ha, do you remember where to go?
357,Taki
Huh?...Ah!
358,Tsukasa
Wait a second. Was that you, Tsukasa? Are you
the one that's been messing with my phone?
359,Taki
Uh... Never mind.
360,Taki
Later.
361,Shinta
Well, he's back to normal.
362,Tsukasa
I think he was kinda... cute yesterday.
363,Taki
Uhhhhh....
364,Taki
Uh... what's up?
365,Staff
Don't play dumb.
What about bro code, huh?!
366,Staff
Yeah, you walked home
with her yesterday, right?
367,Taki
Uh, what are you talking about?
Me and Ms. Okudera?
368,Staff
- So what did you guys do?!
369,Taki
Uh, well... I don't remember, actually.
370,Staff
Quit messin' around and tell us!
371,Okudera
Okudera, reporting for duty!
372,Okudera+Staff
-Don't slack off today, you guys.
We're gonna have a good day today.
-Yeah...
373,Okudera
Aren't we, Taki?
374,Staff
Hmmm?
375,None
"Mitsuha? Who are you?? What are you??"
376,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: I see you're not touching
your boobies today.
377,Yotsuha
Breakfast time! Hurry up!
378,Mitsuha
MY BOOBS?!
379,Mitsuha
Mornin'!
380,Mitsuha
I feel like everyone's
starin' at me for some reason.
381,Saya+Mitsuha
- Well you did kinda make a scene yesterday.
- Uh?!
382,None
"Still-life drawing"
383,StudentB
-Did you see all the election posters?
384,StudentA
-Doesn't matter who wins, nothin'll
change, 'cept for who gets the kickback.
385,StudentB
-Shhh! Somebody's daddy's dependent on it.
386,Taki
-They're talking about me, right?
387,Saya
Uh... [Nod]
388,Mitsuha
Wait, Mitsuha?!
389,Mitsuha
I... I...
390,Mitsuha
I did what?!
391,Yotsuha
Mitsuha?
392,None
"What is this life?"
393,Mitsuha
Could this... could this mean-
394,Taki
-No, no, no, no! Could this mean...
that we're really-
395,Mitsuha
That we're...
in our dreams, that guy and I-
396,Taki
That we're...
in our dreams, that girl and I-
397,None
"Life in Tokyo"
398,None
"What is this life?"
399,Taki+Mitsuha
- We're switching places?!
400,Band
At last, hello, you've opened your eyes,
401,Band
but why won't you even look me in the eyes,
what's wrong with you?
402,Band
You angrily tell me that I'm late.
403,Band
Well, I'm sorry, but I did my best
and running at my fastest pace!
404,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: I'm slowly beginning to
realize what's going on.
405,Mitsuha
Taki's in high school and living in Tokyo.
406,Taki
Taki: Two or three times a week, I'll suddenly and randomly
switch with Mitsuha, who's somewhere out in the boonies.
407,Taki
The trigger is sleep. The cause is unknown.
408,None
"Condition: Sleep? Cause: Unknown"
409,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Any memories I have of the switch
get more and more hazy after I wake up.
410,Taki
Taki: But there's no doubt that
we're switching places.
411,Taki
The reactions of everyone
around us prove it.
412,Taki
And that's why...
413,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: That's why we decided to lay out some ground
rules so we could protect each other's way of life.
414,None
"Strictly forbidden!"
415,None
"No baths! No looking! No touching!"
416,Mitsuha
Things to watch out for during the switches,
and a list of stuff we should never do.
417,None
"Don't waste money!
No dialect! Don't be late!"
418,Taki
Taki: We also agreed to leave each other reports
on our phones on the days we switch places...
419,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: So that we can work together to get
through this... weird thing that's happening.
420,Mitsuha
-And yet...
421,Taki
422,Mitsuha+Taki
- I cannot believe this guy!
- I cannot believe this girl!
423,Band
Back in the Zenzenzense 'til this day,
424,Band
been looking everywhere for you.
425,Band
I followed the sound of
your innocent laughter,
426,Band
and it guided me in the right way.
427,Band
Even if every piece of you disappeared
428,Band
and if it scattered everywhere...
429,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Guys will stare. Watch the skirt!
430,Mitsuha
These are basics for a girl!
431,None
"Careful with skirts!"
432,Taki+Mitsuha
Taki: Stop wasting my money on sweets!
Mitsuha: It's goin' in your body.
Plus, I also worked for that money.
433,None
"Braided Cords..."
434,Taki
Taki: Braiding cords is impossible!
435,Mitsuha+Taki
Mitsuha: You work way too many shifts!
Taki: 'Cause you keep wasting money!
436,Band
I wonder if we can push our way through
437,Band
the countless barrier that's waiting
in the future just beyond our view.
438,Band
Side-by-side, no way we can lose.
439,Band
We'll beat destiny at its own game
and make it follow our own rules.
440,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Had tea with Ms. Okudera on the
way home. You two have a good thing going!
441,Taki
Taki: Quit messing with my
relationships, Mitsuha!
442,Mitsuha
-Hey, Taki... why is a girl
confessing her love to me?
443,Taki
-Maybe you're just more
popular when I'm you.
444,Mitsuha
-You're so full of yourself!
Like you have a girlfriend!
445,None
"Don't be so full of yourself!!"
446,Taki
-It's not like you have anyone, either!
447,Taki+Mitsuha
- I don't...
448,None
"Dummy"
449,None
"Idiot"
450,Mitsuha+Taki
- Because I don't want a relationship!
451,Taki
I shouldn't for her sake.
452,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: You sure do like your own boobies.
453,Yotsuha
Time to go! Get ready!
454,TV
Over the course of the last few days, the Tiamat comet
has been visible, but when and where can people see it?
455,None
"Comet Tiamat to Reach Perigee"
456,TV
The Tiamat comet will be moving in the same direction
the sun does: from East to West from our point of view.
457,Yotsuha
Why are you wearin' your uniform?
458,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: Grandma, why does our shrine god's
relic have to be kept so far away?
459,Grandma
'Cause of Mayugoro, I don't really know.
460,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- Who's Mayugoro?
- What? He's famous!
461,Mitsuha
Hop on, grandma.
462,Yotsuha+Mitsuha
- Oh!
- Watch out! Careful!
463,Grandma
Mitsuha. Yotsuha. Do you know about Musubi?
464,Mitsuha
Mu... subi?
465,Grandma
It's what we used to call the local guardian
deity long ago, and it means "union".
466,Grandma
This word has profound meaning.
467,Grandma
Tying strings together is a union, connecting to
people is a union, and the flow of time is a union.
468,Grandma
These are all part of the god's power. The
braided cords that we make are tied to that.
469,Grandma
A skill from the god,
they represent the flow of time itself.
470,Grandma
They assemble and take shape. They twist,
tangle, unravel now and then, break...
471,Grandma
and reconnect.
472,Grandma
That's what a union is. What time is.
473,Grandma+Mitsuha
- Have a drink.
- Thanks.
474,Yotsuha+Grandma
- I want some, too!
- That's also a union.
475,Grandma
Whether it's water, rice or sake, when something
becomes a part of a person, it's a union.
476,Grandma
It joins their soul, which is why the offering
we're making today is such an important custom.
477,Grandma
It connects the god with people.
478,Yotsuha
Hey, I can see it!
479,Mitsuha
This is where it is.
The sacred relic of Miyamizu Shrine.
480,Grandma
What lies ahead is the hereafter.
It's the netherworld.
481,Yotsuha
The netherworld!
482,Grandma
In order to return to this world, you have to
leave behind what is most important to you.
483,Grandma
Like the kuchikamizake.
484,Mitsuha
Kuchikamizake?
485,Grandma
You'll offer it at the foot of the shrine
god's relic. After all, it is half of you.
486,Mitsuha
Half... of Mitsuha.
487,Yotsuha
Wow, it's already magic hour!
488,Mitsuha
Magic hour?
489,Yotsuha+Mitsuha
- Oh, yeah! Maybe I can see the comet!
- Huh? The comet?
490,Grandma
Oh, Mitsuha...
491,Grandma
you're dreaming right now, aren't you?
492,Taki
I'm crying? But why?
493,None
"I'm almost there. Looking forward to it!"
494,Taki
Ms. Okudera? She's almost where?
495,Taki
Oh, Mitsuha. What did you do?
496,Taki
Date?!
497,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: "Tomorrow's your Tokyo date with Ms.
Okudera."
498,None
"Meet up at the station at 10:30!"
499,Mitsuha
Well, that's what I had planned, but...
500,Okudera+Taki
- Hi, Taki.
- Huh? Agh!
501,Okudera+Taki
- Wait long?
- Yeah. Aah-no! Uh...
502,Taki+Okudera
- I just got here.
- Thank goodness. Let's go!
503,Mitsuha
Must be nice.
They've probably met up about now.
504,Mitsuha
Huh?
505,Mitsuha
Why am I...?
506,Mitsuha
Why...?
507,Mitsuha
"It was a date I wanted to go on, but if it so happens that
you end up goin', you better be grateful and enjoy it!"
508,Taki
This is nice! It's my first time here.
So, is this one of your usual go-to spots?
509,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: "At any rate, I bet you've
never even been on a single date."
510,Taki
No way, it's too expensive!
511,Taki
I don't know what to say to her.
512,Mitsuha
"That's why I've handpicked some links
below to help you out, ya wallflower!"
513,Taki
For real?
514,None
"You, too, can get a girlfriend!"
515,None
"Despite social anxiety, I got a girl!"
"The dos and don'ts of texting!"
516,Taki
She's making fun of me!
517,None
"Photo Exhibition: Nostalgia"
518,Okudera
You know something, Taki?
519,Okudera
Today, you're...
you're like a different person.
520,Taki
Ms. Okudera. You getting hungry?
We could get dinner.
521,Okudera+Taki
- Uh... let's call it a day.
- U-uh... Alright.
522,Okudera+Taki
- I could be wrong, and I'm sorry if I am...
- About?
523,Okudera
But you used to have a
little crush on me, am I right?
524,Okudera
But right now,
there's someone else you like, huh?
525,Taki+Okudera
- N-n-no! U-uh-it's not that...
- Really?
526,Taki+Okudera
- There's no one. It's not like that.
- Are you sure about that?
527,Okudera
Well, thanks for today. See you at work!
528,Taki
Taki: By the time the date's over,
529,Taki+Mitsuha
-you should be able to
see the comet in the sky.
-"...you should be able to
see the comet in the sky."
530,Taki
What does she mean? Weirdo.
531,Mitsuha
-Oh.
532,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: It's you, Teshi.
533,Mitsuha
No. I just didn't feel like
goin', that's all. I'm fine.
534,Mitsuha
What? The festival?
535,Mitsuha
Ah...
536,Mitsuha
Oh yeah, the comet.
It'll be at its brightest today, right?
537,Mitsuha
Okay, got it. Seeya later!
538,Saya
You're just looking forward to seeing
Mitsuha in a yukata, aren'tcha?
539,Teshi
I- I am not!
540,Teshi
I mean, it didn't even cross my mind.
541,Teshi+Mitsuha
- Y'know, she sounded kinda down when I talked to her.
- Maybe she just didn't want a call from ya.
542,Teshi
It's not funny!
543,Mitsuha+Teshi+Saya
- Sorry to keep ya.
- Oh, she's here!
- You're late!
544,Saya+Teshi
- [Gasp]
545,Saya+Teshi
- Mitsuha, what happened to-?
- [Gasp]
546,Teshi
-Your hair!
547,Mitsuha
I guess... it's weird.
548,Teshi
You think it's gotta do with some guy.
Like, he broke her heart?
549,Saya
Guys always just assume that
it has to do with a boy.
550,Saya+Teshi
- She said she felt like cuttin' it.
- Ya sure about that? You really think she
felt like cuttin' off that much of it?
551,Mitsuha
Hey guys, I can see it!
552,Mitsuha+Saya+Teshi
- Whoa, ho-ho!
- Whoa...
- Ah.
553,Mitsuha
Huh?
554,Phone
Phone: "The number you are trying to reach is currently
outside the cellular network or has been turned off due-"
555,Taki
Taki: I'll just have to tell her how lousy
the date ended up the next time we switch.
556,Taki
That's what I thought.
557,Taki
But, for some reason,
558,Taki
the switches Mitsuha and I had
been going through until now...
559,Taki
they never happened again.
560,None
"Mountains in Gifu Prefecture"
561,None
"Hida Mountains"
562,Taki
Wha-
563,Taki
What are-
564,Taki
What are you doing here?
565,Okudera
Okudera: Tsukasa told me about it, so here I am.
566,Taki
I asked for two things: to cover my shift
and to back up my alibi if my dad asked.
567,Tsukasa
Relax, Takagi's gonna take your shift.
568,Takagi
Takagi: Gotch'a covered!
569,Takagi
But you owe me dinner.
570,Taki+Tsukasa
- So, you're all in on it...
- You've got everyone worried about you.
571,Taki+Tsukasa
- Huh?
- We can't ignore this! What if somebody's
trying to pull one over on you?
572,Taki
Like catfish?
573,Okudera
I mean, you met this person
online, didn't you?
574,Taki
No, not exactly! It's kinda complicated.
575,Tsukasa
- Could be from a dating site-
- She's NOT!
576,Tsukasa
It's because you've been acting awfully
fishy lately, so we're keeping an eye on you.
577,Taki
I don't need a babysitter, okay!
578,Taki
Taki: The switches stopped, my calls never
connected, and texts never went through.
579,Taki
That's why I decided to
go see Mitsuha in person.
580,Taki
I wanted to see her, but...
581,Okudera
-What? You don't know where she is exactly?
The town's landscape is your only clue?
582,Taki
Yeah.
583,Okudera
And you can't contact her?
What's that about?
584,Taki+Tsukasa
-Where are we?
You're a terrible tour guide-
-'Cause I'm not one!
585,Okudera
Oh, well. Guess we'll help you search.
586,Okudera+Taki
- Aww, it's so cute! Look, Taki!
- Seriously, guys?
587,Okudera
Okudera: It moved! Awww!
588,Taki
Taki: This is a lost cause.
589,Okudera+Tsukasa
- What?!
590,Okudera
After everything that
we've done for you today?!
591,Taki
You haven't done anything!
592,Okudera+Tsukasa
- One Takayama Ramen.
593,Taki
I guess I'll have the same.
594,Waitress
Sure.
595,Waitress+Chef
Waitress: Three orders of ramen.
Chef: Got it.
596,Taki+Tsukasa
- Think we can make it
back to Tokyo tonight?
- Well, I think we'll be cuttin' it close.
597,Tsukasa
Let me take a look.
598,Taki+Okudera
- K, thanks.
- Wait, Taki. You sure about that?
599,Taki
Yeah. I kinda feel like maybe I've been
barking up the wrong tree this whole time.
600,Waitress
Hey, that's a sketch of Itomori, isn't it?
601,Waitress
It's drawn really well.
602,Waitress
Come take a look at this, hon!
603,Chef
Yeah, that's Itomori. Takes me back.
604,Waitress
My husband was born and raised
there, you know.
605,Taki
Itomori?
606,Taki
Yes, of course! That's the place!
It's nearby, right?
607,Waitress
You don't...?
608,Chef
Itomori was...
609,Tsukasa
Itomori...[Gasp]
610,Tsukasa+Okudera
- But that's where-!
- Wait! Isn't that the
area where that comet-?
611,Taki
Huh?
612,None
"Keep Out"
613,Okudera
Hey...
614,Okudera
Okudera: Is this place really where she's from?
615,Tsukasa
Tsukasa: No way. Taki must have just
confused this with somewhere else.
616,Taki
Taki: No, I didn't.
617,Taki
This was the place.
618,Taki
The schoolyard, these mountains,
619,Taki
even this high school here!
620,Taki
I remember it all!
621,Tsukasa
There's no way you could.
622,Tsukasa
You've gotta know about that
disaster three years ago, right?
623,Tsukasa+Taki
- Hundreds of people died.
- They died...
624,Taki
three years ago?
625,Taki
It can't be...
626,Taki
There's no way...
627,Taki
I mean...
628,Taki
I still have the memos she wrote.
629,Taki
They're fading.
630,Tsukasa
Comet Tiamat, with an orbital period
of 1,200 years,
631,None
"Itomori, the Town that Vanished"
632,Tsukasa
made a close approach to Earth
three years ago in October.
633,None
"Meteor Strikes, Wipes out Town"
634,Tsukasa
Nobody foresaw that its nucleus
would split at its perigee.
635,None
"Town Annihilated"
636,None
"Over 500 dead or missing"
637,None
"Itomori, the Town that Vanished"
638,Tsukasa
A fragment that broke off of it
became a meteor and struck Japan.
639,None
"Itomori, comet, damage"
640,Okudera
It looks like that day was the
same date as the Autumn Festival.
641,Tsukasa
The point of impact was here.
642,Tsukasa
At 8:42 PM (20:42), it fell right around
where people were gathered for the festival.
643,None
"Names of the Victims"
644,Tsukasa
Over 500 died.
645,Tsukasa
It was a third of the town's population,
646,Tsukasa
and now, nobody lives in Itomori anymore.
647,Taki
Teshigawara...
648,Taki
and Sayaka.
649,None
"Mitsuha Miyamizu"
650,Okudera
That's her?!
651,Okudera
You were wrong! You gotta be!
652,Okudera
After all,
this girl here died three years ago!
653,Taki
Just... two or three weeks ago,
she said that I'd be able to see the comet.
654,Taki
That means-!
655,Grandma+Taki
- "You're dreaming right now... aren't you?"
- I...
656,Taki
I...
657,Taki
What...
658,Taki
was I?
659,Okudera
Sounds lively over there.
660,Tsukasa
They only have one room left.
I'm really sorry.
661,Okudera
It's not a problem.
662,Okudera
How's Taki?
663,Tsukasa
He's still reading articles on Itomori.
664,Tsukasa
He's goin' through all those newspapers
and magazines at random. Seems obsessive.
665,Okudera+Tsukasa
- What is it?
- Oh, sorry. You smoke, huh?
666,Okudera
Yeah. I did quit at one point.
667,Tsukasa
What do you think about
what Taki's been saying?
668,Okudera
I had feelings for him, y'know.
669,Okudera
The way he's been recently.
670,Okudera
I mean, he was a nice guy
before, but he's even nicer now.
671,Okudera
Kind-of... frantic.
672,Okudera
It was cute.
673,Okudera
Although, I do think what he's been
telling us is definitely strange-sounding.
674,Okudera
But in the end, the fact remains that Taki's met
someone, and that someone is the reason he changed.
675,Okudera
That much is for sure.
676,None
"Worst-Ever Itomori Comet Disaster"
677,Taki
It was all just a dream.
678,Taki
I recognized the landscape
679,Taki
because I unconsciously remembered
the news from three years ago.
680,Taki
If it's not that, is she... a ghost?
681,Taki
Or...
682,Taki
did I just make it up?
683,Taki
The whole thing?
684,Taki
What was her name?
685,Taki
I can't remember.
686,Okudera
Tsukasa said he was gonna
go ahead and take a bath.
687,Taki
Ms. Okudera,
688,Taki
Uh...
689,Taki
I, um...
690,Taki
I realize I've been saying
a lot of strange things.
691,Taki
I'm really sorry, and thank you.
692,None
"The Tatara Iron-Making Site"
693,None
"The Braided Cords of Itomori"
694,Okudera
Braided cords. Pretty.
695,Okudera
That band on your wrist.
696,Okudera+Taki
- That's one, isn't it?
- Hm? Oh.
697,Taki
This thing? Guess so.
698,Taki
Somebody...
699,Taki
Someone gave it to me.
700,Taki
I wear it sometimes as...
kind-of a lucky charm.
701,Okudera
Who was it?
702,Okudera+Taki
- It's late. Why don't you go
down and take a bath, too?
- Sure-wait.
703,Taki
Yeah. Someone who makes these,
704,Taki
they once told me something.
705,Taki
The cords represent the flow of time.
706,Taki
They twist and tangle,
707,Taki
unravel and connect,
708,Taki
and that's what time is.
709,Taki
Maybe if I could-
710,None
"Around here?"
711,Mitsuha
Taki...
712,Mitsuha
Distant Voice: Taki.
713,Mitsuha
Taki!
714,Mitsuha
Don't you remember?!
715,Okudera
[Gasp]
716,None
"I have to go somewhere. Go back to Tokyo
without me. I'll return later. Thanks."
717,Okudera
Taki...
718,Chef
Eat this bento up there.
719,Chef
Your drawing of Itomori.
You did a real good job.
720,Taki
-They assemble and take shape,
721,Taki
they twist, tangle,
722,Taki
unravel now and then,
723,Taki
break,
724,Taki
and reconnect.
725,Taki
That's what a union is.
726,Taki
What time is.
727,Taki
There it is.
728,Taki
It's really there!
729,Taki
It wasn't...
730,Taki
a dream.
731,Taki
What lies ahead is the netherworld.
732,Taki
It's still here.
733,Taki
This was Yotsuha's, and this was mine.
734,Taki
This was before the comet.
735,Taki
So when I switched places with her,
736,Taki
it was also three years in the past.
737,Taki
Our times... got tangled somehow.
738,Taki
This is... half of her.
739,Taki
Musubi,
740,Taki
if it's true, and time can be unraveled,
741,Taki
just give me one more chance.
742,Taki
Agh!
743,Taki
[Gasp]
744,Taki
A comet!
745,Taki
ngh! Hh...
746,None
[Heartbeat]
747,Mitsuha+Futaba
- [Crying]
- Your name's going to be...
748,Futaba
Mitsuha.
749,Toshiki
Both of you are my treasures.
750,Futaba
You're going to be a big sister!
751,None
"Get well soon, Mom!"
752,MitsuhaMom
I'm so sorry, my dears...
753,Yotsuha
Dad, when is mommy coming home?
754,Toshiki+Grandma
- I couldn't help her!
- Get ahold of yourself!
755,Toshiki+Grandma
- Who cares about the shrine?!
- But you're in charge now!
756,Toshiki+Grandma
- I loved Futaba, not Miyamizu Shrine!
- Get out!
757,Grandma
Now listen to me, girls.
758,Grandma
Starting today,
you'll be living with grandma.
759,Mitsuha
"Who are you?"
760,Mitsuha
"Who am I?" Who are you?
761,Mitsuha
"Mitsuha"
762,Mitsuha
"Idiot"
763,Mitsuha
Don't be full of yourself!
764,Mitsuha
Like you have a girlfriend!
765,Mitsuha
Must be nice.
766,Mitsuha
They've probably met up about now.
767,Mitsuha
Why am I...?
768,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- I'm going to Tokyo.
- What?! Wait, Sis!
769,Mitsuha
Grandma?
770,Mitsuha
Would you mind doing me a favor?
771,Mitsuha
Oh yeah, the comet.
772,Mitsuha
It'll be at its brightest today, right?
773,Taki
-Mitsuha, don't go there!
774,Taki
Mitsuha!
775,Taki
You've gotta get out of town
before the comet strikes!
776,Taki
[Gasp]
777,Taki
Mitsuha, run!
778,Taki
Mitsuha! Mitsuha! Mitsuha!
779,Mitsuha
[Gasp]
780,Mitsuha
Taki (as Mitsuha): Mitsuha.
781,Mitsuha
She's alive!
782,Mitsuha
[Sobbing]
783,Yotsuha
Let me guess, you're touching your boo-
784,Yotsuha
[Gasp]
785,Mitsuha
[Crying] Her sister!
786,Mitsuha
Yotsuha!
787,Yotsuha
Yotsuha: Ungh!
788,Yotsuha
[Shudder]
789,Yotsuha
I think she's finally lost it.
790,Yotsuha
Just for today,
I-I'm gonna head out first...
791,Yotsuha
She's lost it...
792,Yotsuha
Really lost it...
793,Yotsuha
Totally!
794,Yotsuha
Totally...
795,TV
-For all you stargazers out there, the comet Tiamat
has been visible to the naked eye for about a week now.
796,TV
Tonight, it will finally reach its perigee around 7:40 PM (19:40),
and be at its maximum brightness when viewed from the Earth's...
797,Mitsuha
It's tonight! There's still time left!
798,Grandma
Mornin', Mitsuha!
799,Grandma
What's this?
800,Grandma
Hold on...
801,Grandma+Mitsuha
- You're not Mitsuha, are you?
- W-wait, how did you-?
802,Mitsuha
You already knew?
803,Grandma
No, but watching the way you've been
behaving lately stirred some memories up.
804,Gradnma
When I was a young girl,
805,Grandma
I had some pretty strange dreams myself.
806,Mitsuha
Huh?
807,Grandma
Though it's been so long, the memories of who I became
in those dreams have pretty much faded at this point.
808,Mitsuha
Faded?
809,Grandma
Treasure the experience.
Dreams eventually will fade away.
810,Grandma
I went through similar times myself,
811,Grandma
and so did your mother.
812,Mitsuha
What if...
813,Mitsuha
all those dreams that
the Miyamizu people had!
814,Mitsuha
It had to do with today!
815,Mitsuha
Grandma, you have to listen to me!
816,Mitsuha
Tonight,
817,Mitsuha
the comet is going to fall on Itomori!
818,Mitsuha+Grandma
- You're all gonna die!
- Huh?
819,Mitsuha
"Nobody's gonna believe that?"
820,Mitsuha
I didn't expect that out
of Mitsuha's grandma.
821,Mitsuha
It doesn't matter!
There's no way I'm gonna let them all die!
822,Saya
Mitsuha!
823,Saya
What happened... to-?
824,Teshi
What'd you-?
825,Teshi
Your hair!
826,Mitsuha+Teshi
-Ugh, the haircut?
Looked better before, huh?
-No, i-i-it's good!
827,Mitsuha
Nevermind that! If we don't do
something about tonight, we'll all die!
828,Mitsuha
It's up to us to save everyone!
829,Shopkeeper
Wait, shouldn't you be in school?
830,Saya
Well, we sort-of have to save the
town, or something.
831,Shopkeeper
Heh?
832,Mitsuha+Teshi
- The warning system?
- Yeah, those speakers all over the town.
833,None
"Superimposition, frequency"
834,Mitsuha
I get it. It could work!
835,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Niiiice job, Teshi.
- Hey, I don't think you should
be sittin' so close to me.
836,Mitsuha+Teshi
- What's wrong. Uh-oh! You shyyy?
- Would you quit it?!
837,Teshi
It ain't proper and you know it!
838,None
"Club Discontinued - Keep Out"
839,Mitsuha
Taki (as Mitsuha): T-hahahahaha!
840,Mitsuha
Such a gentleman.
841,Saya
I bought all the snacks, guys.
842,Saya+Mitsuha
- Here's the change.
- Sorry for the trouble.
843,Saya
I didn't mind.
844,Teshi+Mitsuha
- We oughta be gettin' paid.
- Quit complaining.
845,Saya
So? Wha'dcha come up with?
846,Saya
Got an evacuation plan?
847,Saya
A- A-
848,Saya
A BOMB?!
849,Teshi
Yeah, we have water gel explosives we
use for construction at our storage site.
850,Saya
AND the warning system?
851,Teshi
Our startup frequency can hijack the
town's warning system pretty easily,
852,Mitsuha
so we can broadcast an evacuation warning
for the whole town right from school!
853,Mitsuha
Look, we're outside the disaster area here,
854,Mitsuha
so we'll just make an announcement
to evacuate to the school.
855,Saya
It's-
856,Saya+Mistuha
- It's totally a crime!
- You'll be in charge
of the broadcast, Saya.
857,Saya+Teshi
- Why me?!
- You're in the Broadcast Club.
858,Teshi+Mitsuha
- And I'll be in charge of the explosives.
- While I go have a word with the mayor.
859,Saya+Teshi
- Why?
- 'Cause if the evacuation order's not comin' from Town Hall, then nobody's gonna go anyway.
860,Mitsuha
But if I talk to the mayor,
as his daughter, I can convince him.
861,Saya
It's the perfect plan!
862,Saya
Fine, I don't really care
one way or the other.
863,Saya
This is just a theory of yours, right?
864,Teshi
Well...
865,Teshi
Theories can be based on reality. Like, do you know the
story of how Itomori Lake was formed? It's a crater!
866,None
"A meteor crater lake
formed 1,200 years ago."
867,Teshi+Mitsuha
- That means a meteor hit this area
at least once a thousand years ago!
- Right. That's why-!
868,Mitsuha
Nice one, Teshi!
869,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Let's go evacuate the town!
870,Toshiki
Mitsuha's Father: What on earth
are you talking about?!
871,Mitsuha
Like I said,
872,Toshiki+Mitsuha
-We have to evacuate everyone
in town before tonight or else-
-Enough! Shut up!
873,Toshiki
"The comet's going to split
in two and strike the town?"
874,None
"Itomori Town Hall"
875,Toshiki
"Over 500 will die?"
876,Toshiki
How dare you stand there
and spout such nonsense!
877,Toshiki
If you're serious, you must be sick!
878,Toshiki
I guess recklessness is a Miyamizu trait.
879,Toshiki
I'll have a car take you to the
city hospital for an examination.
880,Toshiki
We will continue this discussion
after you've seen a doctor.
881,Mitsuha
You!
882,Mitsuha
You son of a- !
883,Toshiki
Mitsuha's Father: Mitsuha...
884,Toshiki
No...
885,Toshiki
Wait a minute...
886,Toshiki
Who are you?
887,Kids
-I'll see you guys at the festival, ba-bye!
-We'll meet ya at the step stone shrine.
Don't be late, k?
888,Kids
- Ba-bye!
- Seeya!
- Later!
889,Mitsuha
You shouldn't go!
890,Mitsuha+Kids
-You've got to leave town!
Tell all of your friends!
-What's wrong with you?!
891,Yotsuha+Mitsuha+Kids
- Mitsuha!
- What was that about?
- Come on, let's go.
892,Yotsuha
What are you doing, huh?
893,Mitsuha
If it was Mitsuha,
894,Mitsuha
would she have been able to convince him?
895,Mitsuha
- Is all this my fault?!
- Huh?!
896,Mitsuha
Yotsuha, promise me that you'll
leave town with grandma before dark!
897,Yotsuha
What?!
898,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- You're gonna die if you stay here!
- What are you talking about?!
899,Yotsuha
And why did you suddenly go to Tokyo yesterday?!
You've been acting really strange lately!
900,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- Went to Tokyo?
- Hey! Mitsuha!
901,Teshi
How'd it go with your old man?
902,Teshi
Hey, Mitsuha!
903,Teshi
What's with your sister?
904,Yotsuha
Don't know.
905,None
[Ding]
906,Mitsuha
Could she be over there?
907,Sara
What's that? What's over there?
908,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Let me use your bike, Teshi.
- Hey.
909,Teshi
Mitsuha.
910,Teshi
And what do we do?
911,Mitsuha
Get things ready like we planned!
912,Mitsuha
I'm counting on you!
913,Taki
Mitsuha: Oh my gosh! I'm Taki again!
914,Taki
What's Taki doin' out here?
915,Taki
The town!
916,Taki
It's gone!
917,Taki
So...
918,Taki
does that mean...
919,Taki
I... died?!
920,Mitsuha
"Taki."
921,Mitsuha
"Taki!"
922,Mitsuha
"Don't you remember?!"
923,Mitsuha
I'm going to Tokyo for a few hours.
924,Yotsuha
Wha? Right now?
925,Mitsuha+Yotsuha
- But why?
- Uh...
926,Mitsuha
For a date.
927,Yotsuha+Mitsuha
- You have a boyfriend in Tokyo?!
- I-I didn't say it was a date for me.
928,Mitsuha
"I'll be back tonight."
929,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: If I suddenly show up, will it
be a nuisance or a surprise?
930,Mitsuha
He might not like it if I do.
931,Phone
"The number you are trying to reach
is currently outside the cellular network."
932,Mitsuha
I guess it won't happen, but...
933,Mitsuha
What if it did?
934,Mitsuha
What would I do?
935,Mitsuha
Would I annoy him?
936,None
"Tiamat Makes
Closest Approach Tomorrow"
937,Mitsuha
Would it be awkward, or maybe...
938,Mitsuha
he'd be glad to see me.
939,Phone
"The number you are trying to reach
is currently outside the cellular network."
940,Mitsuha
I guess we won't meet.
941,Mitsuha
But... there's one thing I'm certain of.
942,Mitsuha
If we see each other,
943,Mitsuha
We'll definitely know right away...
944,Mitsuha
that you were the one who was in me,
945,Mitsuha
and that I was the one who was in...
946,Mitsuha
- you.
- Sorry!
947,Mitsuha
[Gasp]
948,Mitsuha
'Scuse me.
949,Mitsuha
Taki: Agh!
950,Mitsuha
That time...
951,Mitsuha
three years ago.
952,Mitsuha
Before I even knew you...
953,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: [Whispering] Taki...
954,Mitsuha
Taki?
955,Mitsuha+Taki
- Taki!
- Huh?
956,Mitsuha
Uh... It's me!
957,Mitsuha+Taki
- Don't you... remember?
- Uh...
958,Taki
Sorry, who are you?
959,Mitsuha
I- I'm sorry.
960,Mitsuha
Ah!
961,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: But, he's Taki!
962,Taki
Taki: What a weird girl.
963,Conductor
Train announcer: "Yotsuya. Yotsuya.
Stay clear of the doors."
964,Mitsuha+Taki
- Hold on!
- Huh?
965,Mitsuha+Taki
- Egh!
- What's your name?
966,Mitsuha
Mitsuha!
967,Mitsuha
My name is...
968,Mitsuha
"Mitsuha!"
969,Mitsuha
Taki (as Mitsuha): Three years ago...
970,Mitsuha
you showed up.
971,Mitsuha
It was... to see me!
972,Taki
Mitsuha (as Taki): Taki.
973,Mitsuha
[Echoing] Mitsuha!
974,Taki
Taki?
975,Mitsuha
Mitsuha!
976,Mitsuha
You're here, right?
977,Mitsuha
Inside my body?
978,Taki
Taki?!
979,Taki
Taki, where are you?!
980,Mitsuha
Taki (as Mitsuha): That was Mitsuha.
981,Mitsuha
I can hear her voice, but...
982,Taki
Taki, where are you?
983,Taki
Taki!!
984,None
[Ding]
985,Mitsuha+Taki
- Uh!
- Huh?
986,Taki+Mitsuha
Mitsuha (as Taki): Taki, are you...?
Taki (as Mitsuha)i: Are you there?
987,Taki+Mitsuha
- Magic hour.
988,Taki+Mitsuha
[Gasp]
989,Taki
Uh...
990,Taki
Taki: Mitsuha.
991,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Taki.
992,Mitsuha
Taki!
993,Mitsuha
[Sobbing] You're really here!
994,Mitsuha+Taki
- Taki!
- I came all this way to see you,
995,Taki
which wasn't easy...
996,Taki
since you were pretty far away.
997,Mitsuha
How is that even...?
998,Mitsuha
Because, back then!
999,Taki
Well, I drank some of your kuchikamizake.
1000,Mitsuha
Huh?
1001,Taki
Oh...
1002,Mitsuha
You... you drank that?!
1003,Taki
Huh?
1004,Mitsuha
- STUPID PERVERT!
- Wha-WHA?!
1005,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Yeah, that's right! You were
touching my boobies, WEREN'T YOU?!
1006,Taki
Taki: WHA- ?!
1007,Taki+Mitsuha
- Wha-ho-how do you even- ?!
- 'Cause Yotsuha saw you!
1008,Taki
I just-I couldn't help myself!
1009,Mitsuha+Taki
- But it was just the one time!
- "Just the one time?"
1010,Mitsuha
How many times is it the issue?!
1011,Taki
Sorry!
1012,Mitsuha
Wait...
1013,Mitsuha
Is that...?
1014,Taki
Oh.
1015,Taki
Yeah, it's yours,
but you visited before I knew you.
1016,Taki
So, I didn't know who you were.
1017,Taki
Here.
1018,Taki
I kept it for three years,
1019,Taki
but I think it's time you got it back.
1020,Taki+Mitsuha
- Whaddya think?
- Oh, uh, well...
1021,Taki+Mitsuha
- it's not bad.
- Oh, you're lyin'!
1022,Taki
Busted!
1023,Mitsuha
Why you gotta be like that?
1024,Mitsuha+Taki
- [Laughing]
1025,Taki
Hey, Mitsuha.
1026,Taki
You still have a lot to do.
1027,Taki
Listen.
1028,Mitsuha+Taki
- It's coming.
- Don't worry.
1029,Taki
- You still have enough time.
- [Nod]
1030,Mitsuha
I'll do my best.
1031,Mitsuha
It looks like magic hour is almost...
1032,Taki
over.
1033,Taki
Hey, Mitsuha.
1034,Taki
Just so we don't forget
things when we wake up...
1035,Taki
Let's write down our names.
1036,Taki
Here.
1037,Taki
Mitsuha.
1038,Taki
Hey.
1039,Taki
Mitsuha?
1040,Taki
I was planning to tell you...
1041,Taki
that wherever you are in the world,
1042,Taki
I swear that I'll find you
again, no matter what.
1043,Taki
Your name...
1044,Taki
is Mitsuha.
1045,Taki
It'll be okay!
1046,Taki
I'll remember!
1047,Taki
Mitsuha.
1048,Taki
1049,Taki
Mitsuha!
1050,Taki
Your name is Mitsuha!
1051,Taki
Your name is-!
1052,Taki
Who...
1053,Taki
are you?
1054,Taki
And what...
1055,Taki
did I even come here for?
1056,Taki
I came...
1057,Taki
I came all this way to see her!
1058,Taki
I came to save her!
1059,Taki
I wanted her to be alive!
1060,Taki
Who was it again?
1061,Taki
Who?
1062,Taki
Who did I come to see?
1063,Taki
Someone precious!
1064,Taki
Someone I don't wanna forget!
1065,Taki
Someone I shouldn't!
1066,Taki
Who was it?
1067,Taki
Who was it?!
1068,Taki
Who?!
1069,Taki
1070,Taki
What's your name?!
1071,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Taki.
1072,Mitsuha
Taki.
1073,Mitsuha
1074,Mitsuha
It'll be fine!
1075,Mitsuha
I remember!
1076,Mitsuha
I'll never forget!
1077,Mitsuha
Taki.
1078,Mitsuha
1079,Mitsuha
Your name is...
1080,Mitsuha
Taki!
1081,None
"Itomori Substation"
1082,Mitsuha
Teshi!
1083,Mitsuha
Mitsuha!
1084,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Where the heck have you been?
- He said sorry for breakin' your bike.
1085,Teshi
Wha? Who did?
1086,Mitsuha
I did!
1087,Teshi
You're gonna have to
explain it to me later.
1088,Teshi
That thing is gonna fall, right?
1089,Teshi+Mitsuha
- For real?
- For real. I saw it with my own eyes.
1090,Teshi
What? You did, huh?
1091,Teshi
Well, I guess it's settled, then.
1092,Teshi
We're both officially criminals.
1093,None
"Broadcasting Room"
1094,Saya
What?! Do I really have to...?!
1095,Teshi
Once the town's power goes out, the emergency
generator should kick in right away.
1096,Teshi
Use the broadcast equipment once it does.
1097,Mitsuha
Don't be scared, Saya!
And repeat it as many times as you can!
1098,Teshi
Woo-hoo!
1099,Teshi+Saya
- You can do it!
- Aw, nuts! It's do or die!
1100,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Shouldn't it be goin' off?
- Hell if I know!
1101,Mitsuha+Teshi
- Oooh...
- Ha ha!
1102,Crowd
- What was that?
- It was pretty loud, too.
1103,Crowd
Look over there!
1104,Crowd
- Hey look, up there!
- Whoa!
1105,Sara
This is Itomori Town Hall!
1106,Sara+Crowd
- Reports of an explosion at
the substation are coming in!
- An explosion? Did I hear that right?
1107,Sara
Wildfires are possible,
as well as the threat of more explosions!
1108,Sara
Residents in the followin' areas, please
evacuate to Itomori High School immediately.
1109,Sara
Kadoiri District.
1110,Sara+Crowd
- Sakagami District!
- Honey, we should go.
1111,Sara
The broadcast isn't coming from us?
Well, who the hell is it, then?
1112,Sara
Miyamori District.
1113,Sara
Oyazawa District.
1114,Teshi
Let's go, Mitsuha!
1115,Mitsuha
Teshi!
1116,Teshi+Mitsuha
- Everyone, run! There's a wildfire!
- Wildfire, please run!
1117,Teshi+Mitsuha
- Get outta here! Run, there's a fire!
- It's not safe here! Please, evacuate!
1118,Teshi
It's not workin',
we're runnin' out of time!
1119,Teshi+Mitsuha
- Mitsuha!
- [Sobbing]
1120,Teshi
What's wrong?
1121,Teshi
What is it...?
1122,Mitsuha
I can't remember what his name is anymore!
1123,Teshi
What is with you?!
You're the one who started all of this!
1124,Teshi
We can't evacuate everyone
without firefighters!
1125,Teshi
Get goin'! You gotta convince your old man!
1126,Teshi
Everybody, get to the high school! HURRY!
1127,Crowd
Oh, it's Mitsuha.
1128,Crowd
-Why would terrorists attack way out here?
What is Chubu Electric saying?
-They're still checking.
1129,Toshiki
Any update? No wildfires yet?
1130,Toshiki
You sure? Got it.
1131,Toshiki
Make them stop this broadcast immediately!
Haven't you located its source yet?
1132,Crowd
Mayor, the Takayama sensor
station just called!
1133,Toshiki
From the high school?
1134,Sara
Once again, residents in the following
areas, please evacuate to Itomori High...
1135,Crowd
- Ah!
- What are you doing?! Turn that off!
1136,Mitsuha+Teshi
- They got Saya!
- Oh no.
1137,Crowd
What were you thinking, Natori?! I swear!
1138,TownHall
This is Itomori Town Hall.
1139,TownHall
We are currently confirming
the reports of the accident.
1140,TownHall+Crowd
- We instruct all residents to remain calm and stay where they are until further notice.
- I guess... we have to stay put?
1141,Firefighters
- What is goin' on?
- So stay on standby.
1142,Teshi
Come on! They said everyone should evacuate!
The high school's the evacuation center!
1143,TeshiDad
-Katsuhiko!
1144,TeshiDad
Tell me...
1145,TeshiDad
What do you think you're doing?!
1146,Teshi
Sorry, Mitsuha.
1147,Teshi
This is the end.
1148,Teshi
[Gasp]
1149,Teshi
Oh, my God!
1150,Teshi
It's actually splittin' apart!
1151,TV
Look at that! The comet has split into two large
parts and meteors are now falling to Earth!
1152,TV
- Uh, I don't believe anyone
could have predicted this.
- Either way, we have
quite the mystical view here.
1153,TV
-So, what does the comet's
nucleus splitting mean for us?
1154,TV
-The comet's not within the Roche limit, so the nucleus
itself must've had a structural weakness for this to happen.
1155,TV
-Comet Shoemaker-Levy 9 broke apart
and collided with Jupiter in 1994.
1156,TV+Mitsuha
- There were at least 21 fragments...
- I'm going outside to take a look.
1157,TV
- The fragments will likely burn up
well before reaching the ground.
- Does it pose a danger?
1158,TV
-Probability of a meteor actually landing
on a populated area is quite small.
1159,TV
-never foresaw this development.
1160,TV
- To predict the trajectory...
- As we stand here witnessing
this spectacle,
1161,TV
unassisted...
1162,TV
and with our bare eyes,
1163,TV
it strikes me that living in such an age
has never felt more fortunate than now.
1164,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: Hey...
1165,Mitsuha
Who...
1166,Mitsuha
are you?
1167,Mitsuha
Who?
1168,Mitsuha
1169,Mitsuha
Who is he?
1170,Mitsuha
Someone precious.
1171,Mitsuha
Someone I shouldn't forget!
1172,Mitsuha
Someone I didn't want to!
1173,Mitsuha
Who?
1174,Mitsuha
Who?!
1175,Mitsuha
Who are you?!
1176,Mitsuha
What's your name?!
1177,Mitsuha
Oh no!
1178,Mitsuha
Ah! Argh!
1179,Mitsuha
Ungh!
1180,Taki
-"So that we don't forget
things when we wake up..."
1181,Taki
"Let's write down our names."
1182,None
"I love you"
1183,Mitsuha
Writing this...
1184,Mitsuha
doesn't help!
1185,Mitsuha
I won't know your name...
1186,Mitsuha
[Crying]
1187,Mitsuha
Dad!
1188,Mitsuha
- Mitsuha.
- There you are!
1189,Toshiki
Don't tell me you're back!
1190,Toshiki
Ah...
1191,Taki
-"It was almost like seeing
something out of a dream."
1192,Taki
"Nothing more or less..."
1193,Taki
"than a breathtaking view."
1194,Band
Words like "tomorrow"
or "future" or "fate",
1195,Band
no matter how far they extend their hands,
1196,Band
we breathe, we dream, we raise our love
1197,Band
in a timeless land
that is far out of reach.
1198,Band
Even the second, hour hands of the clock.
1199,Band
They look at us sideways
as they tick and tock.
1200,Band
How I hope to have
forever to spend this life,
1201,Band
no- all future lives
1202,Band
right here in this world with you!
1203,Taki
Taki: Huh?
1204,Taki
Why am I here?
1205,Taki
What am I... doing?
1206,Taki
[Gasp]
1207,Taki
U-uh!
1208,TrainAnnouncer
Train Announcer: "The doors are closing.
Please be careful."
1209,Taki
Taki: I'm always searching for something.
1210,Taki
This... feeling has consumed me...
1211,Taki
for some time.
1212,Taki
The reason I applied for this position-
1213,Taki
The landscapes people live in-
1214,Taki
To build a city's landscape-
1215,Taki
Even Tokyo. It might vanish too one day.
1216,Taki
And so, I wanna make landscapes
that- how should I put this?
1217,Taki
That can continue to warm peoples' hearts.
1218,Taki
[Sigh]
1219,Takagi
Takagi: That bad? How many does that make it?
1220,Taki+Tsukasa
Taki: I've stopped counting.
Tsukasa: Doesn't sound too promising.
1221,Taki+Shinta
- Who asked you?
- That suit could be the problem.
1222,Taki
-It looks just like yours!
1223,Taki+Shinta
- Well, I have two offers.
- I have eight myself.
1224,None
"LINE: You have a new message."
1225,Taki
Taki: Is what I'm searching for...
1226,Taki
someone?
1227,Taki
Or somewhere?
1228,Taki
Or am I just searching
for the right job?
1229,Taki
I don't even really know.
1230,Taki
Oh!
1231,Okudera+Taki
- You're job hunting, huh?
- I haven't had much luck, though.
1232,Okudera+Taki
- Hey, maybe it's the suit
that's killing your chances.
- Uh-does it really look that bad on me?
1233,Taki
-So, why the sudden call today?
1234,Okudera
-I was in the area for work and I figured
it had been a while since I saw your face.
1235,None
"8 years since the comet disaster"
1236,Okudera
Okudera: Remember that one time when we
went all the way to Itomori?
1237,Okudera
You were still in high school back
then, so it was...
1238,Okudera+Taki
- Heh. Five years ago.
- That long?
1239,Okudera
It seems like...
1240,Okudera
I've forgotten a lot.
1241,Taki
Taki: I don't... remember all that much,
either.
1242,Taki
About back then.
1243,Taki
Maybe we argued.
1244,Taki
She and Tsukasa went
back to Tokyo without me.
1245,Taki
I spent the night alone on some mountain.
1246,Taki
That's about all I remember.
1247,Taki
But, at one point in time, I found myself strangely
drawn to the incident involving that comet.
1248,Taki
A fragment of the comet destroyed
a town in that disaster,
1249,None
"Evacuation of residents to
high school grounds confirmed."
1250,Taki
but, miraculously,
1251,Taki
most of the people living
in the town were unhurt.
1252,Taki
The town happened to be holding
an emergency drill that day,
1253,None
"No deaths, 104 wounded"
1254,None
"An unprecedented natural disaster"
1255,Taki
and most of its residents
were outside the impact zone.
1256,None
"Residents safe"
1257,None
"Disaster Foretold?"
1258,Taki
The sheer luck and coincidence of it
all sparked various conspiracy theories.
1259,None
"Mayor Miyamizu's hidden agenda"
1260,Taki
I read a lot articles about it back then.
1261,None
"Mysterious explosion at the substation"
1262,Taki
I was kind-of obsessed.
1263,Taki
But whatever the reason I had for my
interest... is a mystery to me now.
1264,Taki
I didn't even know anybody in that town.
1265,Okudera
Thanks for today. This is far enough.
1266,Okudera
I do hope,
1267,Okudera
that at some point,
1268,Okudera
you'll find happiness, too.
1269,Taki
I feel like I'm always searching.
1270,Taki
For something.
1271,Taki
Someone.
1272,None
"Construction company job interview"
1273,Saya
I feel like I do wanna go
to one more bridal fair.
1274,Saya
They're all the same!
1275,Teshi+Saya
- A Shinto weddin' sure sounds nice, too!
- You said you wanted to
be married in a chapel!
1276,Teshi+Saya
- Oh, that reminds me, Teshi!
- Uh!
1277,Saya
Would ya please shave before the ceremony?
I'm goin' on a diet for it, you know.
1278,Teshi
She says as she's eatin' a cake!
1279,Teshi+Saya
- I'll get serious tomorrow.
- Uh...
1280,None
[Ding]
1281,Taki
[Gasp]
1282,Taki
[Sigh]
1283,None
"Itomori, the Town that Vanished"
1284,None
"October 4, 2013 - Itomori Vanished"
1285,None
"Kadoiri Bridge"
1286,None
"Itomori Elementary School"
1287,None
"Miyamizu Shrine"
1288,Taki
Taki: The landscape of a town
that's no longer there.
1289,Taki
Why does looking at it make
my chest feel so tight?
1290,Band
Now, just a little more,
1291,Band
only just a little more.
1292,Band
Let's stay here a little longer now.
1293,Band
Just a little more,
1294,Band
only just a little more.
1295,Band
Let's stick together
just a little bit longer.
1296,Band
Just a little more,
1297,Band
only just a little more.
1298,Band
Let's stay here a little longer now.
1299,Band
Now just a little more,
1300,Band
only just a little more.
1301,Band
Let's stick together
just a little bit longer.
1302,Taki+Mitsuha
Taki: I was always searching...
Mitsuha: Searching for...
1303,Mitsuha
-someone!
1304,Band
Oh yes, we are time fliers,
1305,Band
scaling the walls of time. Climber
1306,Band
tired of playing
hide-and-seek with time and
1307,Band
always comin' dead short.
1308,Band
I'll never let you go now,
1309,Band
promise I will never let you go now,
1310,Band
'cause my hand finally has reached yours!
1311,Band
Why should I have to?
1312,Band
Oh, you're sure quite a showy crier.
1313,Band
Wanna stop your tears,
1314,Band
see your eyes drier.
1315,Band
But when I went to wipe your tears dry,
1316,Band
you refused, but I saw them
pouring down your face, I knew why.
1317,Band
Crying even when you're happy,
1318,Band
smiling even when you're feeling lonely.
1319,Band
It's because a part of you
1320,Band
has made it here before the rest has.
1321,Taki
Taki: Excuse me!
1322,Taki
Haven't we...?
1323,Taki
Have I...
1324,Taki
met you somewhere?
1325,Mitsuha
Mitsuha: I thought so, too!
1326,Mitsuha+Taki
- Can I ask you...
1327,Mitsuha+Taki
- your name?
1328,Band
The sorrowful gust of wind that
blew right between you and me,
1329,Band
where did it find the loneliness
it carried on the breeze?
1330,Band
Looking up at the sky after
shedding a stream of tears,
1331,Band
I could see for miles of blue,
it's never been so clear.
1332,Band
Speeches that my father gave me
would always make me despair.
1333,Band
Somehow, I feel a warmth and comfort today.
1334,Band
Your ever kind heart, the way you smile,
and even how you find your dreams.
1335,Band
I knew nothing, so honestly,
I've always copied you.
1336,Band
Now, just a little more,
1337,Band
only just a little more.
1338,Band
Let's stay here a little longer now.
1339,Band
Now just a little more,
1340,Band
only just a little more.
1341,Band
Let's stick together
just a little bit longer.
1342,Band
Oh yes, we are time fliers
1343,Band
scaling the walls of time. Climber
1344,Band
tired of playing hide-and-seek
with time and
1345,Band
always comin' dead short.
1346,Band
Crying even when you're happy,
1347,Band
smiling even when you're feeling lonely.
1348,Band
It's because a part of you has
made it here before the rest has.
1349,Band
I used to wish upon the stars,
the toys that I once adored.
1350,Band
Forgotten now, are rollin'
'round the corners of the floor.
1351,Band
Finally, my dream has counted
up to a hundred today.
1352,Band
Someday, I'll trade them
all for just the very one.
1353,Band
Girl that I have seen in school,
that never have told "hello",
1354,Band
After class today, I waved and
said, “See you tomorrow!”
1355,Band
It's not really that bad trying
something new every once in a while,
1356,Band
especially if I can do
it with you by my side.
1357,Band
Now just a little more,
1358,Band
only just a little more.
1359,Band
Let's stay here a little longer now.
1360,Band
Just a little more,
1361,Band
only just a little more.
1362,Band
Let's stick together
just a little bit longer.
1363,Band
Oh yes, we are time fliers, so, and I...
1364,Band
I knew who you were way before...
1365,Band
way before I even knew my own name.
1366,Band
There's no clue, but I'm sure. I swear!
1367,Band
Even if you're not around
in this wide world,
1368,Band
of course it surely would
have some kind of meaning.
1369,Band
But if when you're not
around in this crazy world,
1370,Band
would be like the month of
August without summer break.
1371,Band
And if you're not around
in this great world,
1372,Band
would be like Santa Claus without any glee.
1373,Band
If you're not around in this wide world!
1374,Band
Oh yes, we are time fliers
1375,Band
scaling the walls of time. Climber
1376,Band
tired of playing hide-and-seek
with time and
1377,Band
always comin' dead short.
1378,Band
No, never mind that!
1379,Band
No, never mind what I said now,
1380,Band
'cause I'm on my way to you!
1381,Band
Oh, we are time fliers,
1382,Band
dashing up the steps of time now!
1383,Band
No more playing hide-and-seek
with you and time
1384,Band
and always comin' dead short!
1385,Band
You're quite a showy crier!
1386,Band
Wanna stop your tears,
1387,Band
see your eyes drier!
1388,Band
But when I went to wipe your tears dry,
1389,Band
you refused but I saw them pouring
down your face, I knew why!
1390,Band
Crying even when I'm happy,
1391,Band
smiling even when I'm feeling lonely!
1392,Band
It's because the heart of mine
1393,Band
has made it here before my body.